good afternoon, good, look, I
добрый день добрый то вот смотрите я из
’ll ask people from russia from ukraine how you feel
украины людей из россии спрошу как вы
about the war in ukraine,
относитесь к войне в украине
in general, it’s like it doesn’t matter to me,
я вообще мне как бы без разницы дела нет
but the military man or not, or the cadets, I
но же военный или нет или кадетов срочку
don’t serve urgently, I would very much first be sent
служу не отправляется очень бы сначала
not to look at which troops the top is close  how
не смотреть каких войск топ близко как
they don’t send
они не отправляют
it, that is, how it is, but since people
то есть так него а вот так как вас люди
support this war they don’t support
поддерживают эту войны не поддерживают
you, it seems to me that everyone is somehow
мне кажется все как-то нейтрально
neutral in our country, but you see everything is quiet
относятся у нас же видишь тихо все
in general in the country, no one really says for this
вообще в стране никто особо за это не
who doesn’t watch TV,
говорит кто телевизор не смотрит мне
no one seems to me  he doesn’t even really know for
кажется никто даже особо не знает ни за
what it turns out there is a TV pumping up
что получается там телевизор накачивать
people cars without a TV there I calmly
людей авто без телевизора там спокойно
perceive all this, but I live in a socially
все это воспринимаю но я в общественно
quiet place to enter the army, even so I
спокой живу войти в армии даже так вот
saw the boys in the hospital who were wounded and
видел пацанов госпитале кто ранен и
came saying well, it’s scary
приезжали говорят ну так то страшно
calmer you are there they are with these  then the
спокойней вы там они с этими скими то
rebels fought this with the regular
повстанцами воевали эту с регулярной
army in a completely different way, everyone meets
армии совсем по-другому все встречают
well sometimes they meet in the sense of
неплохо иногда встречаются в смысле
oncoming fire to give you well, yes, u  it’s
встречный огонь дать вы ну да у нас в
normal for us to be armed, that is, as it were,
вооружении нормально есть то есть как бы
but look
а вот смотри
at our government so far you have
на наше правительство пока что у вас там
losses there of more than twenty thousand people,
потери там больше двадцати тысяч людей
is it true or is it ours when deceiving and so
это правда или это наши при обман и так
it seems to me if the loss is like a handbrake
ты мне кажется если потерю как ручник
crap but I don’t think it’s so  damn
но я не думаю что это так
because yesterday I talked with the
потому что вот я вчера общался с
girls of their parents in the
девчонками них родителей в
tank troops somewhere near Kharkov did
танковых войсках где-то под харьковом ли
you sin in their city they have a
ты грешил в ихней город у них там на
town there in Altai that 28 thousand people live
алтае городок у это 28 тысяч людей живет
there a military unit looks like 200 grams
там воинская часть выглядит 200 граммов
it came like
пришло типа
you already know everything  but I don’t think that the window is
ты и так все знаю но я не думаю что окно
full of thousands, although everything is possible in general, the
гуж тысяч хотя все возможно в целом
war is so serious,
война то такая серьезная
you know this text from the sofa they are sitting, they
знаете этот текст с дивана сидят они
say no, this is not a war, this is a
говорят нет это не война это
special operation
спецоперации
on TV called a special operation, but in
по телику называют спецоперация но по
fact it is a full-scale war, that is,
сути это полномасштабная война то есть
they sank an aircraft there, he cruiser cruiser
они авиацией там он крейсер крейсер
sank  that is, they are, but with this
потопили то есть они это а вот с этим
cruiser, Moscow, how people relate, well,
крейсером москва как люди относятся ну
how they react to one thing that I still
как реагирует одну что я до сих пор не
can’t almost not only today, in general,
могу почти не только сегодня вообще про
learn about it from roulette told me  and I’m
это узнать от рулетки мне рассказали я
just, well, a civilian, I
просто как бы ну человек гражданский я в
don’t understand these matters, but I
этих делах не понимаю но я так
imagined that this is a cruiser, this is a
представлял себе что это крейсер это
duck and a colossus, this is a HIV strain so that it
утка и махина это штамм вич чтоб на штаб
seems to be like that at the fleet headquarters, that is, he
флота вроде был так то есть у него там
must have some kind of escorted boats
катера сопровождении какие-то должны
on the water  when you drowned it, it’s
быть по воде при как как потопили вы ее
easy to understand, and even without having it, I also
просто понять и даже не имея я тоже за
don’t rummage over the seas the address of which
моря не шарю адрес каких войсках
air force a large plane is excited
воздушных возбуждается большой самолет
or there is a landing party I
или там десант
follow the sky
слежу за небом покаяться понял смотришь
the tula doesn’t like it in ours,
сбрасывали на города тулячка в нашей не
he’s rich, he catches so the
любит он богат ловит так что
British and I don’t
хреновый вам британцы и янь я в них не
understand them alive, so it’s not because I can’t
разбираюсь так не потому что я не могу
understand maple laziness, but I
понять кленовый ленив и но больше я в
’m not an expert in this anymore, but they supply it
этом не специалист но поставляют
takes into account shorter traps, these
учитывает короче ловушки вот эти
thermal attachés  drops a
тепловые атташе сбрасывает
helicopter for example
вертолет например
it shoots down
оно сбивает
because stars tequila star peek somehow
потому что stars текиле star peek как-то
it is called before the british british and i
оно называется до британцы британцы и я
saw i read that full i don't understand
видел я читал что полная я не разбираюсь
technical  characteristics, I can’t
технических характеристиках я не могу
rate a good one, you’re not a Croatian, you’re an
оценить хороший не хорват вы как
air specialist, yes, you can
специалист по воздуху да вот вы можете
nobody, and as I understand it, yours don’t
nobody и я так понимаю что ваши уже не
really want to fly there, it’s
очень хотят летать там
one thing how in Syria to make 300
одно дело до как в сирии сделать 300
raids over these Bedouins tones in the field
налетов над этими бедуинами тонов в поле
where they shoot with Kalash  it’s top
где они с калашами стреляет он верхнего
and another thing when
и другое дело когда
because the tanks, well, these g
потому что танки вот ну это эти g
villins and on low already everyone there knows so they
виллины и on low уже все там знают так в
have learned to impudence and
этом наглостью научились и отличаются
already differ and saw the video how they bought it, but with
уже и видео видели как купили а вот с
these British ones they only saw about the
этими британскими до видели лишь о
news that they came she
новостях показывают что они пришли she
people have already been trained even someone else there is a
люди уже обучены еще даже кого-то там
helicopter as a writer what is it
вертолет ка ка писатель как он
called or co2
называется или co2
helicopter your alligator class
вертолет ваш класс аллигатора
has already been shot down from this thing like yes yes I know
уже с этой штуки сбили типа да да я знаю
and
а
not because of the anti-tank ball
не за то что из противотанковое бальный
plane I have not heard it is interesting
самолет я не слышал это интересно
with us on purpose let's say  we have a very big
у нас нарочно скажем у нас очень большая
motivation among the military, that is, when,
мотивация у военных то есть когда
for example, many Russians do not understand
например многие русские не понимают
why this war is and so the soldier was
зачем эта война и так вот солдат вот его
sent here he has an order, he’s a damn thing
сюда послали у него есть приказ он блин
here, the motivation is clear  yes, for an
тут мотивация понятно да
ordinary
обычным жителем
resident, this joke about Chernobaevka that there
вот этот прикол про чернобаевка что там
seems to be already there 15 or some time, but
вроде как уже там 15 или какой раз но
you know, this is the reason for the combat about the hip,
знаете это причина боевку про бедром
yes, I told you first when there is the third
да то я тебя сначала когда там третий
or fourth time when you hang based
или четвертый раз когда висишь основана
Chernobaevka artillery covered Dublin
чернобаев ки артиллерии накрыли дублин
from this joke there and not  maybe it’s like that
от это прикол там и не может такого быть
and then there is a conversion that
а потом есть конверсия что русские вот
these Russian soldiers who don’t want to fight, they’re
эти солдаты которые не хотят воевать они
specially old equipment again, a helicopter,
специально старой технику снова вертолет
otherwise there’s nothing on the bike on their connectors,
иначе на байке их разъемы нет вертолета
yes, because the girls there also told the
да потому что он там тоже рассказывали
girls their father was on this trip to a
девчонки у них отец в этом в поход к в
big non-tank  gasoline will roll around the village,
большой не танком вокруг села покатается
all the gasoline will fall out, there is no
покатается бензин выпали все бензина нет
type of going anywhere at gas stations,
типа никуда ехать на автозаправках
because before the motivation we have an
потому что до мотивация у нас
unequivocal motivation, such as we came to
однозначная мотивация типа вот пришли
Moscow, but we are defending our land here,
москве но нашу землю мы защищаемся тут
even no one has any doubt, but I didn’t
даже ни у кого не возникает сомнение а
understand how they think,
вот мне непонятно было как бы чем мыслят
let’s say  the load is clear that the politicians will be
ну скажем груз ясно что политики будут
grisha here the Nazis Bandera are shorter
гришу тут нацисты бандеровцы короче там
there, that is, again, but for a specific
на то есть опять а вот конкретному
soldier who  about being sent here to
солдат у которого отправляют сюда
die, like, so that's what he thinks, like,
умирать типа так вот что он думает типа
for what type
а за что типа
should he
должна
initially be there to protect
вообще первоначально был там защитить
or Ghanaian
или ганский
then now if you look at
тогда сейчас если смотреть
civilians for the entire time of
мирных жителей в за весь за все время
this conflict, something according to
вот этого конфликта что-то по данным
the same Luhansk and Donetsk something  it’s like
этих же луганска и донецка что-то вроде
100 or 200 suffered in eight years in
100 или 200 пострадала за восемь лет
total from you it turns out in two months
всего от вы получается за два месяца уже
thousands of thousands of people all over Ukraine have already
тысячи тысячи людей по всей украине
suffered children cyprus pancake is also
пострадали детей кипр блин тоже
incomprehensible and from the Russians you
непонятный и от у русских которого
know that for example the military you
знаешь вот то например военные ты
adequately look more sinful I don’t like
адекватно смотр грешнее я типа не
this but  here’s a dude sitting next to this,
отношусь к этому а вот сидит к это чувак
especially somewhere in a village in Siberia,
особенно там где то в селе в сибири
I’m sitting for a war, so that in short, you’re
сидит я за войну чтобы короче вот вам
eleven in the morning, and here you are, and how exactly
утром надцать и вот тебе и как конкретно
do you benefit from understanding him, and damn
тебе какая выгода понять его и вот блин
it, people watch TV enough and want to
она люди насмотрятся телевизор и хотят в
watch the news in Russia, so then
россии смотрят новости так вот тогда
we talked when we just started breeding in the
общались когда только начала разводить
fourteenth year they speak from ukraine
четырнадцатом году они говорят с украины
to you pizdy tells us [ __ ] up that everything is
до вам пиздy нам говорит что все
shorter crap in russia and we are
короче хуёво у россии а нам без дешево
all [ __ ] up without cheap ukraine and  in short, they’ll correct us like this,
украины всех уёба и нас короче вот так
poison, poison on has all
подправят травит травят на has all
parts of toyota television, they are hot in
частиtoyota телевидении они горячие на
Russian, [ __ ] up, in short, and science,
русском короче и наука
that’s good, that’s how these sanctions
вот хорошо вот как вот эти санкции
now hit the people of Miletus, too, everything
сейчас ударили по люди милета тоже все
peter
питер
seems to be more on the companies
кажется больше по компаниям ударила
that the sanctions hit, yes, I don’t look at the
которые санкции да мне на смотри на
needs,
нужды
because  in short, I read right now,
потому что короче вот я щас читал
today it turns out that we have a
сегодня получается у нас же магазин
clothing store there zara
одежды там zara
closed in short all over the country bershka
закрылись короче по всей стране bershka
well, all sorts of things like that and they write here that
ну всякие такие и они тут пишут что мы в
we want to return
ближайшее время мы хотим вернуться
back to the marketplace in Russia in the near future to be
обратно на торговую площадку россию быть
and go and instagram sieves want like
и пойти и instagram ситы хотят типа там
handbags there  and
сумочки и
there is, for example, to understand that according to
есть например понять вот по компании в
the company, there were employees in the company’s share, you understand,
долю компании были работники понимаешь
for example, if there is some kind of conditional
например если есть какая-то там условная
ikea, he had a number of
икея у него была там сколько-то
employees there, if she leaves, they
сотрудников если она уходит они
quit, they are out of work, they also
увольняются они без работы они так также
don’t buy products from someone, that is
у кого-то не покупают продукцию то есть
it costs less money for her, that is,
денег стоит меньше у нее типа то есть
it’s a problem to pour, and
это проблему сыпать а
that is, you don’t buy it, it’s not a miracle, it’s
то есть ян ты не покупаешь не чудо то из
difficult for you to
тебя получается трудно
understand t  oh yes, and you don’t feel it, yes,
понял то есть и ты ее не ощущаешь да
that’s why about the solstices, and
поэтому про солнцестояний а
you have to demobilize, reach a
ты должен демобилизоваться достичь
month or two, well, a bath so that
месяц-два ну ванну чтобы не отправились
people don’t send conscripts to you anymore
в вас люди уже уже срочников не
, you need to send them first, and
отправляют нужно сначала отправляли а
then to this noise you went here, ours
потом к это шум у вас пошел вот наши
began capturing these muscles,
начали пленных этих мышц
he  he comes in a bunch of hairy tanks,
он приходит кучу он волосистую танка
he surrenders, he doesn’t understand anything at all for
сдается он вообще ничего не понимать для
what combo, this video also went to the village for
чего комбо вот это видео тоже в село за
2pm pawns went there and something else got out with
2pm пешки и еще что-то вылезли с
these villagers in the village agreed
селянами этими в деревне договорились
that they leave on their own and a couple of these
что они своим ходом уходят и пара эти
barrels left and went to  direction
бочки оставили и ушли в направлении
is stored somewhere they are lagging behind their
хранится где-то они отстали от своей
column, I can lose the types well for the sake of
колонны типы потерять хорошо могу ради
what,
чего
because there are a lot of villages, well, as
потому что селах очень много ну как бы
if you were pumped up on TV there people
вот вас по телеку накачивали там людей
here everyone wants Russia here everyone wants
вот тут все хотят россии тут все хотят
Russia so these soldiers come and here it’s
россии так эти солдаты приходят а тут
like in Kherson  they showed, you can see the
вон как в херсоне показывали можно видел
video they went to kherson to people and with
видео зашли в херсона людям и с флагами
Ukrainian flags climbs on an armored personnel carrier and like on a
вылазит украинскими на бтр и типа на
tank like these all the same and arut they went the
танке типа эти все таки и арут им пошли
[ __ ] out of here like on a Russian occupier then
нахуй отсюда типа на русский оккупант то
yes, he was going here as if to protect himself from the
есть он ехал сюда как бы защищать от
Nazis,
фашистов
Koroteev’s people came, [ __ ]
приехала люди коротеева пошел нахуй
the template break, this is when there, of course,
разрыв шаблона это когда там конечно
Mariupol is also glass there, let’s say such
мариуполя тоже стекла там скажем такой
how many from our side, how many from your
сколько с нашей стороны сколько с вашей
type died there, no one
типа погибло там еще точно никто не
knows for sure yet for a long time no one will consider
знает еще точно долго никто не посчитает
this and peaceful  mine, so I have an acquaintance,
это и мирных минных так у меня знакомый
yes, yes, and they will count someone for a long time,
ну да да и долго будут считать кого а
but look,
вот смотри
for
например
example, these talks about nuclear strikes, so
вот эти разговоры про ядерные удары так
it’s all like show-off or it really can
это все типа понты или это реально может
be like
быть такое
how much the ato poplar is nuclear,
почем ато тополь это ядерная
because, well, it’s already warm, well, sort of,
потому что как бы ну уже тепло ну вроде
yes it is  it just turns out that, as it were,
да она просто получается что как бы там
Putin declared that they were ready to deliver this
путин заявлял что готовы нанести это
response to a nuclear strike, and he was already
ответ на ядерный удар и он уже начинаешь
starting something, something like,
что-то начнется то типа
well, yes, well, for example, to catch it in her head,
ну да ну например поймать в голове вот
for example,
он например
we don’t know what’s in her head, but he’s for
мы не знаем что у нее в голове так но он
someone  transmits this conditionally order in
кому-то передает этот условно приказ так
this way and this someone already decides to
и этот кто-то уже принимает решение
execute and it’s not sticky, it’s not like that, and
выполнить и не липло не так вот и
for example, if you serve you, a beautiful
например служишь тебе придет прекрасном
cool goal will come to shoot down, for example, you
круто цель сбить например наличие ты же
won’t  think about what kind of goal you
не будешь задумываться что за цель ты
will take and yes, and you will execute
возьмешь и да и
it just like with this bls, a
исполнишь так то так же как с этим bls
civilian plane was
гражданский борт в четырнадцатом году
shot down with a beech over Ukraine in the fourteenth year, that is,
сбили с буком над украины то есть
dudes received an order, they see it as salt,
чувакам пришел приказ они видят солью
or they didn’t even know what type it was
или они даже не знали что там типа было
and their own, that is, that one  who gave the order,
и своего то есть тот кто отдавал приказ
he understood, for example, or didn’t figure it out
он понимал например или не разобрался
, so here it turns out there is a
вот такие тут получается же есть
problem that they can give some kind of
проблема в том что могут отдать какой-то
order during a nuclear strike, so
приказ при ядерный удар так и вот такие
guys like you didn’t send the order
как ты ребята не приказ пришел передал
further, attached pressed here somewhere,
дальше придавал прижал тут где-то там
pressed something  she flew to then
нажал что то она прилетела к потом
understands it, but for example,
разбирается на а вот например как бы вот
how do you think people think that Russia is not
как у вас люди считают они что россия не
so, that is, it’s not just the
так то есть не просто там
leadership of the country’s leadership there, but
руководительство руководство страны а
ordinary people are also responsible for this
простые люди ответственны тоже за эту
war,
войну
they don’t even know well, for example, how do you
даже не в курсе ну вот ты например как
think that there is  is it your fault as a
считает что есть есть твоя вина как
citizen that your country is, as it were,
гражданина в том что твоя страна как бы
fighting against Ukraine,
воюют против украины
I’m talking about,
говорю о
for example, you are a citizen as a person and
например ты как человека гражданин и
do you consider yourself vodka this feeling of
считаешь ли ты себя водку это чувство
guilt due to the fact that your  the trana
вины из-за того что твоя страна напала
attacked another country or not there is such a feeling
на другую страну или нет такого ощущения
in general, probably not, but I see it as a
в целом нету наверное но я видишь как то
neutral attitude who wants to fight,
нейтрально отношусь кто хочет воевать
fights,
воюет
well, it just turns out, as it were, well, on your
ну просто получается как бы ну с вашей
part, some people want to water some
стороны люди некоторые хотят поливать не
who don’t want to at all,
которые вообще не хотят
who wants
кто хочет
me, well, look here there  people are divided
меня ну смотри тут тут есть люди делятся
into those who directly fight those
на тех кто непосредственно воюют те
who support the war and those who are
которые поддерживают войну и те которые
against and not those who, as it were, I’m
против и не те которые как бы я вообще
not in business at all, that is, I think that,
не при делах то есть я считаю что как бы
well, let’s say it’s impossible to be here, I’m like days,
ну скажем тут не можно быть я типа дни
and so that is, when on behalf of there
причем так то есть когда от имени там
your country, for example, if on behalf of
твоей страны вот если например от имени
Ukraine we attacked Moldova, but Moldova,
украины напали мы на молдавию но молдова
I would have time, this is the ecumenical
я бы вот времени это это вот вселенский
attack, and I’m like I’m not in business,
нападает а я как бы я не при делах так
that is, here you need to understand that I
то есть тут надо бы понимать что я нес
would also bear some degree of responsibility
бы тоже какую-то степень ответственности
for that  that my country is falling, well, it
за то что моя страна она падает ну
just turns out that in general, what
просто выходит так что в целом то мы то
we will do is what we’ve
что сделаем тем что вот ему там
got into his head there, we won’t even
сбрендила в голову ему дальше мы даже
tell him about it so that
ему не как об этом не скажем чтобы вот
we need to stop everything  osyat russian
надо прекратить все просят русский
say that it is necessary to finish this we are
скажите что нужно закончить это мы
never
никогда не
given look well, as if your people
дано смотри ну как бы и ваш люди
elect the truth turns out that is, but he
избирает правда получается то есть но он
represents
представляет
this plan
этом план
people vote for even the dead we
люди голосуют по даже мертвый у нас была
also had once when I was to their
тоже когда-то когда я к их янукович был
Yanukovych in some areas  more than
то в некоторых участках больше
once I have never voted honestly for Putin
я вот ни разу за путина не голосовал
to bypass the whole outburst how it turns out
честно выброс обойти весь как получается
all people give the opportunity to
все люди дают возможность
rig elections like this and then, according to the
фальсифицировать выборы так а потом по
results of these rigged
результатам этих фальсифицированных
elections, they suffer because of the fact that,
выборов так они страдают из-за того что
let's say, these people whom they did not
скажем вот эти люди которых они не
elect seem to be like that there  they drew the
избирали вроде как бы так там нарисовали
result, and not on their behalf, I make a war there, they
результат а не от их имени делаю там
send people like that, they die, too,
войну посылают людей так умирают тоже
as it were, well, yes, this is the growth of the people, the
как бы получается ну да это роста народ
people we have without a spirit, and here it is, without a
народ у нас без духа и вот она без душка
darling, we would have a spirit like the Siberians have a year of
был бы у нас дух как у сибиряков год
Siberia in Siberia, the guys generally sent in order
сибири в сибири ребята вообще в порядке
some mayor, in short, from United
прислали какого-то мэра короче с единой
Russia, instead of what they had, they
россии вместо того что у них был
came, they just
приехали чуть
think it’s to
думают это
see what kind of city it’s interesting for
посмотреть что за город интересно
themselves, they didn’t wear this territory is large
себе не не носили эта территория большая
and
и
puts it back in place,
ставит обратно на место не
I don’t know that last year
я знаю что были в прошлом по моему году
in Khabarovsk there were very large tenges behind
в хабаровске очень большими тенге зад
your governor there the
вашу губернатора там
central government pressed you a
центральная власть прессовал вам очень
lot, that is, for us, this is how
много то есть для нас вот как людей из
we watched people from Ukraine, for us it seems
украины мы смотрели для нас это кажется
that in Russia there are such rallies at  I had
что в россии таких митинга при мне было
huge ticks, but it
огромных тиковых а
turns out yes from you, that is, the
получается да от тебя то есть
central part of Russia there,
центральная часть россии там
Moscow-Petersburg, they generally don’t protest,
москва-питер они вообще типа не протест
no, there’s no spirit of people,
нет нет духу людей
but why does it turn out that people in Siberia
ну а почему так получается люди в сибири
there or there in the far line are bolder and
там или там дальнего строке там смелее и
[music]
[музыка]
mentality should be
менталитет и должен быть всех один у там
I can’t say all of them there, it’s just
вообще не могу сказать просто народ
that some people live in Moscow, I don’t
какой-то живёт в москве такой не
like it,
нравится
look around, but there is a
осмотрите а есть
big city
большой город
rich in
богатенький
others, and here’s a Russian death for me
других и вот мне как-то русский гибель
that Moscow is not Russia, that is, Moscow
что москва это не россия то есть москва
and Russia are two different things Muscovites
и россия это две разные вещи москвичей
don’t  and you know, all the same, they live there,
не и себе знаешь все таки там живут там
here is Moscow, like a rich one, in this
вот москва типа богатенькая вот в этом
region and for yourself, well, there is a shorter one, that is,
региона и себе ну есть короче то есть и
ticking, but you were able to get here, here we have
тиканье а вот смогли вас вот у нас
Ukraine, so that is,  we are based on the
украина так то есть у нас в основу
main population, then the Ukrainians are
основное население то украинцы так есть
still here in the Crimea there and the Kherson region
еще вот в крыму там и херсонской области
Crimean Tatars compact settlements
крымские татары компактные поселения
part is Russian, this is us because it was
часть есть русский это нас так как был
settled but during sex, but the
заселен а во время секса а вот
Russian Federation, this method has a
российской федерации этот метод очень
lot of national republics, plus a
много национальных республик плюс очень
lot of people move from the republics  in the
много переезжает из республик в
republic you don’t have these inter-
республике так у вас нет вот этих между
ethnic conflicts and
национальных конфликтов и
I don’t mean there because I remember
не имею ввиду там что потому что я помню
that in the 90s there were Russians against the Chechen
что в 90 были там русские против чеченца
there were Azerbaijanis against the fact that
там азербайджанцы против том что
Russia turns out, that is, it’s not one
россия получается то есть это не одном
national such a multinational
национальная такая многонациональная
country, yes, but of course there are  people
страна да но есть конечно остались люди
who the [ __ ] out of here these chocks all
которые там нахрен отсюда этих чурок все
that
такое
but they don’t go to them from the dandy of the nation to
но и на их их не идут от денди нации
fix and the [ __ ] Ukraine is one
фиксировать а петух украина едина
digits game of people
циферов игра людей
okay and look
окей а смотри
what’s the news of the whale is
что там новости кита
good yes everything is happy on
хорошо да все счастливо на